<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>mawulijo</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on mawulijo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2018 10:03:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Simplifying a Laborous Task With Golang</title>
      <link>/blog/simplifying-laborous-task-with-golang/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2018 10:03:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/simplifying-laborous-task-with-golang/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this post, I am going explain how I used Golang to simplify a daunting task at work.
Before I start, I assume you have basic knowledge in SQL like me :-)
Lets take a look at this query
SELECT [circuit_id],[unique_id],[unique_number],[created_user], [created_date],[last_edited_user],[last_edited_date],[object_id] FROM [&amp;lt;DB_NAME&amp;gt;].[dbo].[&amp;lt;TABLE_NAME&amp;gt;] WHERE unique_id=&#39;1111&#39; OR unique_id=&#39;2934&#39; OR unique_id=&#39;3150&#39; OR unique_id=&#39;3640&#39; ***** thousands of unique_id *****  Obviously, its a simple query, provided you have a few number unique IDs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Movies Catalogue</title>
      <link>/gallery/movies-catalogue/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Dec 2018 14:10:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/gallery/movies-catalogue/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>La-Bezbo</title>
      <link>/gallery/la-bezbo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Dec 2018 13:50:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/gallery/la-bezbo/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SMSfy</title>
      <link>/gallery/smsfy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Dec 2018 13:30:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/gallery/smsfy/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Myself</title>
      <link>/blog/myself/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 08:25:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/myself/</guid>
      <description>Profile I am a full stack web and mobile developer and systems administrator based in Accra, Ghana.
I have been building websites and applications for the past two years and I graduated with my first degree from Switzerland Management Center University (SMCU) with a Bachelor in IT-Security (BBA). I am currently pursuing my second degree in BSc. (Hons) Computer Science at Regent University College of Science and Technology. Defered for a year</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Curriculum Vitae</title>
      <link>/blog/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2018 20:14:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/cv/</guid>
      <description>Profile I am a logical thinker, resourceful and willing to take full ownership of user problems until they are fully resolved. I am hungry to learn Computing and its manifold aspects from the ground up
Professional Background JULY 2013 - Present  IT Assistant - Power Distribution Services Ghana  P.D.S provides electric power to the southern part of Ghana   Few of my duties include:  Provide broad IT related support via remote or in person as needed to minimize downtime 2018: Part of a curated team of individuals for the successful Enterprise Service Bus (ESB) 2017: Part of a curated team of individuals for the successful implementation of Geographic Information System (GIS) 2017: System administrator for the Perfomance Management System (PMS) 2015: Liaise between the I.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2017 17:39:21 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>I am a self driven individual and passionate about computing especially programing. My dream is to become a Software Engineer/Architect.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>