<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on mawulijo</title>
    <link>/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on mawulijo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating a New Theme</title>
      <link>/blog/creating-a-new-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/creating-a-new-theme/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This tutorial will show you how to create a simple theme in Hugo. I assume that you are familiar with HTML, the bash command line, and that you are comfortable using Markdown to format content. I&amp;rsquo;ll explain how Hugo uses templates and how you can organize your templates to create a theme. I won&amp;rsquo;t cover using CSS to style your theme.
We&amp;rsquo;ll start with creating a new site with a very basic template.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Myself</title>
      <link>/blog/myself/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 08:25:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/myself/</guid>
      <description>Profile I am a full stack web and mobile developer and systems administrator based in Accra, Ghana.
I have been building websites and applications for the past two years and I graduated with my first degree from Switzerland Management Center University (SMCU) with a Bachelor in IT-Security (BBA). I am currently pursuing my second degree in BSc. (Hons) Computer Science at Regent University College of Science and Technology
I have worked with the Electricity Company of Ghana for the since 2013 as an IT Assistant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Curriculum Vitae</title>
      <link>/blog/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2018 20:14:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/cv/</guid>
      <description>Profile I am a logical thinker, resourceful and willing to take full ownership of user problems until they are fully resolved. I am hungry to learn Computing and its manifold aspects from the ground up
Professional Background JULY 2013 - Present  IT Assistant - Electricity Company of Ghana  E.C.G provides electric power to the southern part of Ghana   Few of my duties include:  Provide broad IT related support via remote or in person as needed to minimize downtime 2018: Part of a curated team of individuals for the successful Enterprise Service Bus (ESB) 2017: Part of a curated team of individuals for the successful implementation of Geographic Information System (GIS) 2017: System administrator for the Perfomance Management System (PMS) 2015: Liaise between the I.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>